Lewis Nathaniel Chase Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence with Authors, Artists, Musicians, and Actors, 1886-1947 (Box 15-33)
  - Hill, Herbert, W., 1912
  - Hoban, Charles, 1930-1934
  - Hogarth, Georgiana, 1913
  - Hogg, R. M. 1916-1930, (2 folders)
  - Holland, Caroline, 1915-1917 (Box 22)
  - Holland, Sir Sidney, 1913
  - Holman, Amy, 1911-1914
  - Holzhausen, Paul, 1940
  - Hood, Charles Newton, 1908-1914
  - Hood, P. H., 1913-1915, 1927
  - Hooker, Harry M., 1936
  - Hoover, M. M., 1934-1935
  - Hopkins, W. A., 1913
  - Howe, W. D., 1911-1914, 1936-1937
  - Howells, William Dean, 1917
  - Hubbard, Gilbert Ernest, 1925
  - Hubble, Mrs. Edwin Powell, 1929
  - Hudson, W. H., 1911-1915
  - Hummel, Arthur W., 1928, undated
  - Hunt, Violet, 1907-1913
  - Huntington, Ellsworth, 1926
  - Hu Shih, 1921-1927, (2 folders)
  - Hyde, James H., 1909-1912
  - Ingpen, Roger, 1915-1917
  - Inglis, Alexander, 1926-1933
  - Ingram, John H., 1912-1916
  - Jackson, A.V. Williams, 1899-1911
  - Jameson, R. D., undated
  - Jastrow, Joseph, 1919
  - Johnson, Howard Palmer, 1938 (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Sir Reginald F., 1922-1925
  - Jones, Howard Mumford, 1933-1938
  - Jones, Jas. Edmund, 1936
  - de Jonze, Edouard, 1913-1914
  - Kahn, Howard, 1908-1911
  - Kaufman, Nick, 1911
  - Kellogg, Paul, 1928
  - Kellogg, Sara Fuller, 1926
  - Kilpatrick, William H., 1933
  - Kin, Yameil, 1921, 1934
  - King, Arthur, 1926
  - King, F. A., undated
  - Koehn, Alfred, 1934
  - Krans, Horatio Sheafe, 1903-1925, 1934-1938
  - Krapp, George Philip, 1925-1926
  - Laing, B. M., 1922-1923
  - Lamborn, E. A. Greening, 1918
  - Lampson, Godfrey Locker, 1920
  - Landi, Countess Zanardi,1914-1915, 1935
  - Lapie, Paul, 1909
  - Lathrop, J. B., 1903, 1914-1917, 1926-1929
  - Lattimore, Owen, 1928-1933
  - Lawrence, E. E., 1919, 1929
  - Le Breton, Andre Victor, 1909-1913
  - Lee, Sir Sidney and Ernest Leeman, 1914-1915, 1931
  - Le Fevre, Louis, 1926-1933
  - Lehmann, G., 1906-1909
  - Leung, George Kin, 1925
  - Lewisohn, Will, 1923-1925
  - Liddell, Mark H., 1909
  - Lindley, E. H., 1906 (Box 24)
  - Locke, A. Audrey, 1915
  - Lovell, Percy W., 1914-1915
  - Loveman, Amy, 1925
  - Low, Sidney, 1914-1916
  - Lucey, Roger M., 1919-1920
  - Mabie, H. W., 1906-1907
  - MacArthur, James, 1906
  - McBryde, John McLaren, 1912
  - MacDonald, Angus, 1910
  - MacLeod, G. Hamilton, 1901-1910
  - MacLeod, Josephine, 1919-1923
  - McMillan, Margaret, 1924-1925
  - MacNair, Hallie, 1931-1933
  - MacNair, Harley Farnsworth, 1924-1936
  - MacNitt, V. V., 1925
  - MacRae, John, 1916
  - Madam, Geoffrey, 1933
  - Malmberg, Madame Aino, 1914-1916, 1933
  - Manchester, Fred W., 1917, 1928, 1934-1939
  - Manley, John M., 1915-1917, 1932
  - Mantell, Robert B., 1927
  - Marriott, Harold Vincent, 1933
  - Marshall, Rachel Alice, 1917
  - Marx, Charles D., 1933
  - Maude, Aylmer, 1912-1915, 1938
  - Maufe, Maud, 1911-1914 (Box 25)
  - Mayne, Ethel Colburn, 1923-1924
  - Mears, Isabella, 1923-1925
  - “Meeting the Megatherium”, 1923
  - Melton, W. F., 1912, 1934-1937
  - Mencken, H. L., 1922-1923
  - Merimee, Ernest, 1911, undated
  - Middleton, George, 1907
  - Milhardet, Georges, 1908-1911
  - Miller, F., 1911-1914
  - Miller, Jessie, 1911-1912
  - Milne, James, 1911-1914
  - Mims, Edwin and Frank Mitchell, 1915, 1931
  - Monroe, Harriet, 1917
  - Monroe, Paul, undated
  - Monroe, Will, 1928-1930
  - Moore, Aimee Osborne, 1912-1914
  - Moore, Charles, 1935
  - Moore, Charles Washington, 1904
  - More, Paul Elmer, 1904-1908, 1936
  - Morgan, G. Campbell, 1927
  - Morgan, William Thomas, 1915
  - Morris, George, 1915
  - Morris, Margaret, 1914-1915
  - Moulton, Richard G., 1905-1908
  - Munro, Walter L., 1932-1939
  - Murdock, Kenneth B., 1936
  - Nairn, John, Robert Nathan and Ernest W. Nelson, 1914-1922, 1930-1931
  - Neeld, Dr. G.A., 1929
  - Nevill, J. C., 1911-1914
  - Nicholson, Meredith, 1903-1906, 1926-1931
  - Nicoll, Josephine, 1925-1928 (Box 26)
  - Nicoll, W. Robertson, 1910-1914, undated
  - Noble, Miriam, 1929, undated
  - Nock, Albert and Thomas Nolan, 1915, 1932
  - Nollen, John Scholte, 1907, 1925
  - Nourse, Mary A., and G. Clarke Nuttall, 1914, undated.
  - Odier, Henri, 1909-1911
  - O'Faolain, Sean, 1928
  - O'Hern, Joseph, 1934-1935
  - O'neill, Aeneas, 1910-1916
  - O'Reilly, Mary Bayle, and Mary Openshaw, 1914
  - Ould, Hermon, and Blanche Ostertag, 1908, 1915, 1923
  - Page, Curtis Hidden, 1914
  - Paradise, Frank Ilsley, 19116-1917
  - Parker, Sir Gilbert, 1914-1916
  - Parry, Duke, 1922
  - Paton, Stewart, 1927
  - Payne, Jessie, 1925
  - Pears, Charles, 1915-1916
  - Peattie, Robert B., undated
  - Peck, Walter E., 1928
  - Pendelton, Robert, 1921-1935
  - Pennell, Mrs. Joseph, 1914-1916
  - Pepler, Douglas, 1909-1914
  - Percy, Lord Eustace, 1927-1928
  - Perry, Bliss, 1933, undated
  - Peterson, John, 1929
  - Phelps, Edith, 1914-1918
  - Phillips, Mary E., 1916-1930
  - Pond, James, 1914, 1923, 1928
  - Porohovshikov, Pierre S., 1930-1931
  - Porter, De Brock, 1911-1914
  - Porter, Lucius, 1923-1924
  - Pound, Louise, 1914-1915
  - Price, Maurice T., 1933-1938
  - Price, Thomas, 1899-1900
  - Proctor, Mary, 1914 (Box 27)
  - Putnam, George H., 1911-1914
  - Putnam's (G.P.)Sons, 1906
  - Quennell, Charles Henry Bourne, 1916-1919
  - Quiggin, E. C., 1913
  - Radet, Georges, 1909-1914
  - Randall, John and Otis E., 1911, 1932-1937
  - Raney, L. A., 1929
  - Rankin, Jeanette, 1931
  - Ransome, Arthur, 1914
  - Rashid, P. Abdur, 1920-1934
  - Ratner, Charles, 1911-1914
  - Rawlings, Marjorie, 1940
  - Reed, Langford, 1925-1928
  - Reid, John, Jean, and S. B., 1924-1925
  - Remer, Charles Frederick, 1921-1933
  - Rendall, Vernon, 1911-1916, 1934-1939
  - Repplier, Agnes, 1933-1937
  - Reyher, Paul, 1908-1911, undated
  - Reynolds, George Fullmer, 1908
  - Rhees, Rush, 1903-1905
  - Rice, Alice, 1909-1917
  - Richards, Irving T., 1932 (Box 28)
  - Richardson, W. S., 1931
  - Richmond, B.L., 1921
  - Richmond, Charles A., 1927-1929
  - Richmond, Winifred, 1933-1939
  - Ridge, W. Sheldon, 1922-1925
  - Rideout, Ransom, 1927
  - Roberts, Christopher, 1930-1931
  - Robertson, David A., 1929
  - Robertson, John George, 1905-1908
  - Robinson, George P., 1917
  - Rogers, Francis, 1906-1911
  - Rosborough, R. R., 1929-1932
  - Rose, Ellsworth E., 1929, undated
  - Rosot, Henry, 1913-1915
  - Routh, James, 1929
  - Rowbotham, Arnold Horrex, 1922
  - Rowntree, Fred, 1911-1917
  - de la Ruelle, A.G., 1913
  - Rush, R. L., 1934
  - Russell, Charles Edward, 1934
  - St. Paul, Renee, 1911-1914
  - Sakanishi, Shio, 1934-1939
  - Sampson, George and Isabel Savory, 1911-1914
  - Sampson, Martin Wright, 1903-1914, 1925-1926
  - Sandburg, Carl, 1917, 1930
  - Scott, Sarah C., 1912-1914
  - Sears, Stephen Frances, 1898-1910
  - Sec, Fog F., 1933-1934
  - Seccombe, Thomas, 1911-1914
  - de Selincourt, Basil and Edward, 1923
  - Selleck, Willard Chamberlain, 1925-1927
  - Serkoff, Vera, 1912-1913
  - Seton, Ernest Thomson, 1918 (Box 29)
  - Seward, Samuel Swayze, 1922-1927
  - Seymour, Hellen, 1930-1939
  - Shacketon, William, 1914
  - Shamel, Archibald Dixon, 1926
  - Sharp, Elizabeth, 1911
  - Shaw, George Bernard, 1910
  - Siren, Oswald, 1922
  - Skeat, Walter William (daughter of), 1911-1912
  - Slade, William A., 1934
  - Smith, C. Alphonso, 1912-1914
  - Smith, Frances Drake, 1923
  - Smith, Frank, 1928
  - Smith, Frederick Miller, 1910
  - Sonnenschein, E. A., 1925-1926
  - Stael-Holstein, 1924
  - Stapfer, Paul, 1909-1913
  - Stedman, Laura, 1911, 1933
  - Stephenson, Henry T., 1913
  - Stevenson, Paul H., 1924-1925
  - Stockdale, Christine, 1910-1914
  - Stockley, Cynthia, 1905-1914 (Box 30)
  - Stoddard, F. H., 1908-1911
  - Stolle, Antonie, 1912
  - Straug, William, 1913, undated
  - Sugden, H. W., 1932-1935
  - Sumichrast, F. C., 1915
  - Sutton, Bertha R., 1912-1914
  - Swinnerton, Frank, 1914-1916
  - Sylvester, George, 1897-1898, 1911-1914
  - Taylor, Henry Osborn, 1911, 1921
  - Thoburn, Helen, 1922
  - Thomas, Carl, 1925-1929
  - Thurston, Edward, 1906-1908
  - Ticknor, Caroline, 1917, 1934-1938
  - Todd, Henry Alfred, 1905
  - Tolman, Richard C., 1931
  - Toplis, W. A., 1897-1907, 1916-1927
  - Travers, Martin, 1915-1916
  - Treat, Payson Jackson, 1921
  - Tsai, Ting Kan, 1925, 1932, undated
  - Turner, John Kenneth, 1922-1923
  - Underhill, John Garrett, 1901-1915, 1934-1937 (Box 31)
  - Valentine, Ruth, 1928
  - Van Den Burgh, John, 1907-1915, 1921-1925
  - Van Hoesen, H. B., 1932-1935
  - Van Renusalaer, John and Miriam Van Waters, 1927-1932
  - Varesi, Masud Ali, 1920
  - de Vargas, Philip and Amelie, 1922, undated
  - Verhoeff, Carolyn, 1908
  - Vick, Edward Colston, 1930
  - Vreeland, William Updike, 1911
  - Vrooman, Carl Schurz, 1912
  - Wainger, Bertrand Max, 1930-1931
  - Wainwright, Beatrice, 1912-1914
  - Waldron, Webb, 1917-1921, 1933-1934
  - Walker, Aurthur, 1911-1913
  - Wallace, Charles William, 1901, 1914-1916
  - Walpole, Hugh, 1911
  - Walton, Clarke W., 1933-1936
  - Ward, Charle E., 1930, undated
  - Ward, E. M., 1915
  - Ward, William, 1910-1917
  - Washburn, Julia Chase, undated
  - Watkins, Arthur Charles, 1906-1911 (Box 32)
  - Watson, Dudley Crafts, 1917, 1929
  - Watson, Edmund Henry, and Robert M. Washburn, 1914, 1937
  - Webling, Ethel, 1924-1929
  - Wellock, Wilfred, 1913-1916
  - Wendell, Barrett, 1908
  - Wernaer, Robert Maximilian, 1936–1938
  - Westbrook, Mrs. Jessie Duncan, 1912
  - Wheeler, H. A., 1916
  - White, Newman I., 1929-1931, 1938-1940
  - Whitman, Sidney, 1912
  - Whitty, J. H., 1911-1937
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, 1930
  - Wildman, Edwin, 1911-1912
  - Williams, Ben, 1933
  - Williams, L. Henderson, 1909-1916, 1937
  - Williams, Stanley, 1929, 1936
  - Willson, Augustus E., 1908
  - Wilson, Aphra, 1911-1914
  - Wilson, J. Dover, 1914-1918
  - Woodhull, Marion, 1906 (Box 33)
  - Woollam, W. Beet, 1915
  - Worden, J. Perry, 1908
  - Wright, F. A., 1923
  - Wright, Hugh K., 1928
  - Wright, Thomas, 1912-1914
  - Wyndham, Horace, 1936
  - “Y” miscellaneous 1907, 1914, 1926-1940
  - Yavorska, Lydia, undated
  - Yeats, Jack B., 1917, 1931-1941, (2 folders)
  - Yoshimatsu, S., 1919
  - Young, A. J., 1927
  - Young, Elizabeth, 1935-1939
  - Young, Ella, 1917, undated
  - Young, F., 1908, 1932-1938
  - Young, Owen D., 1929-1930
  - “Z” miscellaneous, 1928-1930
  - Zipperer, Talmadge, 1933-1935
  - Zucker, A. E., 1921, 1929, 1935, (2 folders)
  - Zung, Sien Tsung, 1938-1939
- General File, 1836-1941 (Box 34-162)
  Miscellaneous correspondence, lecture notes, brochures, clippings and printed matter, student exams, other papers and reports, and related matter.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of person, organization, or subject.
  - “A” miscellaneous, 1909, 1914, 1931-1940 (Box 34)
  - Abbey Theater, 1935-1938
  - Abell, Edward Linus, 1929-1939
  - Abercrombie, Lascelles, 1911, 1922-1940
  - Ability, 1926
  - Abingdon Theater, Virginia, undated
  - Achilles, Augusta, 1928-1939
  - Achilles family, 1927-1941
  - Achilles, Paul S., 1935
  - Adamic, Louis, 1932-1938
  - Adams, Henry, 1938 (Box 35)
  - Adams, Sir John, undated
  - Addresses and Autographs, circa 1910-1935
  - The Adelphi, 1927-1930
  - AE Club, 1936
  - Aesthetics, 1922-1927
  - Agencies, 1927
  - Aiken, Conrad, 1922, 1930-1941
  - Aitken, W. F., undated
  - Akhmatova, Anna, 1924
  - Alderman, Edwin, 1936-1940
  - Aldington, Richard, 1923-1941
  - Aldrich, Allegra, 1936
  - Aldrich, Mrs. B. Streeter, undated
  - “Alien Woman Problem in England Today,” undated
  - Aligarh, UP, 1930
  - Allan, P. B. M., undated
  - Allen, Bertha, 1922
  - Allen, Hervey, 1934-1937
  - Alliance Francaise, 1927
  - America, 1925-1936 (Box 36)
  - American Academy of Political and Social Science, 1925-1927
  - American Biography, 1929, 1935
  - American Book Co., 1905
  - American College Bureau, 1920-1925
  - American Colleges for Girls, 1912
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1929-1930
  - “America from Without,” undated
  - American literature, 1898-1906, 1919-1924, 1933-1936, (2 folders)
  - American literature list, 1930-1932, 1939
  - American miscellaneous, circa 1912-1932
  - American notes, undated
  - American poems, 1936
  - American Revolution, 1924
  - American University, Cairo, Egypt, 1921-1922
  - American Universities Club of London, 1910
  - American women in London, 1914
  - Amisten, Louise P., 1936
  - Anderson, George K., 1935
  - Anderson, J. Redwood, undated
  - Anderson, Robert P., 1926-1928
  - Anderson, Sherwood, 1922-1926, 1937-1941
  - Angell, Sir Norman, 1935
  - Anglo-American first editions, 1935
  - Anglo-Saxon lecture notes, 1899-1900, undated
  - Anthology, 1924-1928, 1936, undated, (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - Anthologies, 1919-1920, undated
  - Anthony, Susan B., 1933-1935
  - Antiquity, claim, 1922-1926
  - Apartments, 1908-1909
  - Application for Peking Union Medical College, Peking, China, 1917
  - Application for teaching position, undated
  - Applications, job inquiries, 1914-1934, (4 folders)
  - Arabia, 1926 (Box 38)
  - Aran Islands, 1935
  - Arbuckle, Mary, 1921
  - Arcady, undated
  - Archer, William, 1921
  - Architecture, 1926
  - Architecture and modern life, 1924
  - Argus de la Presse, 1909
  - Aristo, undated
  - Armstrong, Martin, 1921-1922, 1929-1941
  - Arnold, Julean, 1923-1924
  - Arnold, Matthew, 1899, 1921-1940
  - Art, 1924-1936
  - Art, American, 1934
  - Artwork, 1901, 1911
  - Arthur, King of England, 1928-1930
  - Artificers Guild, 1910-1911
  - Asheville, N.C., 1930-1937, (9 folders) (Box 39)
  - Asia, 1927-1928, 1935
  - Asquith, Herbert, 1918-1920, 1940
  - Atheism, 1933
  - Athenaeum, London, England 1911-1915
  - Athenaeum Bulletin, 1931-1935
  - Atticans, 1932-1934 (Box 40)
  - Atwood, Albert, 1932-1939
  - Auden, W. H., 1935-1940
  - Auslander, Joseph, 1934-1939
  - Austen, Jane, 1922-1927, 1938-1940
  - Austin, Mary, 1922
  - Australia, 1926
  - Authors' Club, Boston, Mass., 1936-1938
  - Authors' Club, London, England, 1909-1910
  - Authors' Club, Washington, D.C., 1935-1937
  - Authors, Incorporated Society of, 1910-1920, (3 folders)
  - “A,” unimportant letters, undated
  - Authors, essays on, undated (Box 41)
  - Authors' League of America, 1912-1913
  - Authors' pictures, 1907-1911
  - Autograph collections, 1936-1937, undated
  - Average Man, 1927
  - Ayscough, Florence, 1921, 1934-1940
  - “B” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1895, 1908-1915, 1922-1940, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1892, 1904, 1931-1937, undated
    - Newspaper clippings, 1912-1940
  - Babbles, 1906, 1916-1940 (Box 42)
  - Bacon, Leonard, 1932, 1938-1941
  - Baerlein, Henri, 1936
  - Baker, LaReine, 1910-1912
  - Bakersfield, my voyage to, 1925
  - Ballads, 1902
  - Banks, Elizabeth, undated
  - Bantock, Raymond, 1919-1927, (3 folders)
  - Barber, C. M., undated (Box 43)
  - Barber, Mrs. Earl, 1933, undated
  - Barckhausen, H. 1897-1901, 1909
  - Barclay, G, 1897
  - Baring, Maurice, 1919-1938
  - Barker, Stephen, 1911-1912
  - Barnett, E. M., 1914-1915
  - Barnett, E. S., 1908-1913
  - Barrie, James, 1924, 1930-1941
  - Basler, Roy P, 1935
  - Bates, A., undated
  - Bates, Katherine Lee, 1930
  - Bau, Joshua M., 1923-1925
  - Baudelaire, Charles, 1905-1907
  - Beard, Charles, 1928-1935
  - Beardsley, Aubrey, 1927
  - Beaumont and Fletcher, 1909
  - Beau-Site Tennis Tournament, 1910
  - Beck, L. Adams, and E. Barrington, undated
  - Beckford, William, 1922, 1928, 1936
  - Bedford Park Literary Society, 1911-1914
  - Beerbohm, Max, 1912
  - Beers Almanack, 1793
  - Beeson, E. M., 1911
  - Behenna, K. A., 1924
  - Bell, Bernard I., 1940
  - Bell, Julian, 1931, 1938
  - Bell, Mackenzie, 1912
  - Bellinger, Mrs. Franz, 1915 (Box 44)
  - Belloc, Hilaire, 1922-1941
  - Benedict, Ruth, 1924-1925
  - Benet, Stephen Vincent, 1928-1941
  - Bennett, Dorothy Graham, 1926-1928, 1938
  - Bennett, James W., 1924-1927
  - Benoit, 1910-1913
  - Benson, A. C., 1913, 1924-1926, 1939
  - Benson, Stella, 1919-1928, 1935
  - Bestsellers, undated
  - Bhavagad, Gita, 1927-1928
  - Bible, 1921-1925, undated
  - Bickerton, A.W., 1916
  - Bierce, Ambrose, circa 1917, 1925-1931, 1937-1939
  - Bille, Anna M., undated
  - Billiards, 1930-1937
  - Bills paid, 1928
  - Binns, Henry Bryan, 1911, 1918-1921, 1927
  - Binyon, Laurence, undated
  - Birmingham, University of, Birmingham, England, 1908 (Box 45)
  - Bishop Della Chiesa and the story of his lost grave, 1923
  - Bishop, John Peale, 1939
  - Bishop, William Henry, undated
  - Bisbee, Genevieve, 1898, 1908-1910
  - Bjouser, undated
  - Black, Josephine, 1938-1941
  - Black Mountain College, Black Mountain, N.C., 1936
  - Blackwell, B. H., 1918-1936
  - Blake, Howard, undated
  - Blake, William, 1906-1936, (8 folders)
  - Blakemore, Trevor 1927, 1936 (Box 46)
  - Blanchard, Frederic T., 1925-1927, 1933
  - Bliss, H. H., 1926-1937
  - Bloomington, Indiana, 1900-1906
  - Bloomsbury House Club, undated
  - Blum, Jean, 1911-1914
  - Blunden, Edmund, 1920-1941
  - Blunt, Wilfrid Scawen, 1923-1938
  - Boats, 1911-1914, (3 folders)
  - Boatwright, F. W., and C. T. Goode, 1929
  - Bodenheim, Maxwell, 1921-1922
  - Boehm, Margaret, 1935-1940 (Box 47)
  - Bolingbrooke, undated
  - Bonded Tobacco Co., 1935
  - Books, 1911-1915
  - Book Club, California, circa 1926
  - Book collecting, 1927-1936
  - Book collectors, 1930
  - Books, 1914, 1930-1933
  - Book reviews, 1912
  - Bookstores, 1923-1937, undated, (3 folders)
  - Booth, Edwin, 1929-1940
  - Bordeaux, 1908-1915, (2 folders) (Box 48)
  - Bottomley, Gordon, 1917-1939
  - Boughton, Rutland C., 1914-1915
  - Bourgeois, Maurice, 1913
  - Boyd, Marion and Mrs. Kenneth, undated
  - Boyesen, Hjalmar H., 1936
  - Boyne Valley, undated
  - Boynton, Grace M., 1922-1929, 1941, (2 folders)
  - Bradford, E. E., 1922
  - Bradley, Andrew C., 1913, 1936-1940
  - Bradley, W. A., circa 1912
  - Bradstreet, Howard, 1937
  - Brandes, Georg, 1906, 1926-1927, 1935
  - Brandl, Von Alois, 1906
  - Le Braz, Mabel Davison, 1936
  - Brede, A., 1923-1925
  - Brede, Ruth Powell, 1925-1926
  - Brentford Gas Co., 1910-1914
  - Brentwood, N.Y., 1891, 1901-1917, (2 folders) (Box 49)
  - Brewster, James, 1929
  - Brieux, Eugene, 1911
  - Brigman, B. M., 1909-1913
  - Bridges, Robert, 1913, 1918, 1925-1941
  - Bridgers, F. A., 1930
  - Great Britain, undated
  - British Academy, 1914
  - British Museum, London, England, 1911-1914
  - British Weekly, 1904-1905
  - British Writers in America, undated
  - Brittany, 1914
  - Bronson, C., 1933-1939
  - Bronson, Marion, 1918-1922
  - Bronte, Patrick Branwell, 1924-1928, 1938-1940 (Box 50)
  - Brooke, Rupert, 1925-1936, (2 folders)
  - Brooke, Stopford A., undated
  - Brooks, Charles S., 1927-1929
  - Brooks, C. Harry, 1924
  - Brooks, Edmund D., 1913-1914
  - Brooks, Van Wyck, 1932-1940
  - Brown, Bob, 1932
  - Brown, Frank Clyde, 1929-1931
  - Brown, Kenneth, undated
  - Brown School, 1928-1929, (2 folders)
  - Browne, Waldo R., 1923, 1929-1930
  - Browning, Elizabeth Barrett, 1905, 1936
  - Browning, Robert, 1899, 1907, 1912, 1920-1940
  - Bryson, Lyman, 1926, 1935-1937
  - Buchan, John, 1926-1931, 1940-1941
  - Buchanan, Angus, 1926
  - Buck, Pearl, 1932-1938
  - Buckton, Alice M., 1938, undated (Box 51)
  - Buckingham, undated
  - Buddhism, 1922-1930, 1937
  - Budgell, Eustace, undated
  - Bungalows, circa 1910-1912
  - Bunyan, John, 1907, 1935, undated
  - Burchell, Albert, 1913
  - Burdick murder, 1903
  - Burgess, Stella Fisher, 1924
  - Burning books, 1912
  - Burns, Robert, 1899-1903, 1928, 1938-1939
  - Burr, Aaron, 1925
  - Burrows, Harold, 1924
  - Burstow, Meg, 1939-1940
  - Burt, Kitty, 1931-1938
  - Butler, Cyrus, undated
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1902, 1923-1928, 1939-1940
  - Butler, Samuel, 1935-1936, undated
  - Butterfield, Frances, 1934-1939
  - Bynner, Witter, 1918-1941 (Box 52)
  - Byrne, Donn, 1929
  - Byron, George G., 1899-1908, 1925-1940, (2 folders)
  - “C” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1906-1940
    - Miscellany, 1901, 1907, 1912, 1923-1925, 1932-1937
    - Nnewspaper clippings, 1920-1940
  - Cabell, James Branch, 1921-1927, 1940 (Box 53)
  - Cady, Joseph, 1930-1937
  - Caesar, Julius, undated
  - Calfee, John, 1932-1936
  - California, undated
  - California Institute of Technology, Pasadena, Calif., 1925-1927
  - California history, undated
  - California State Board of Education, 1926-1927
  - The Caliphates, 1924
  - Caloric stove, 1913
  - Calverley, Charles S., 1928
  - Campbell, Joseph, 1921
  - Campbell, Roy, 1924, 1930
  - Campbell's Fireless Cooker, 1911
  - Canals, American, 1913
  - de Candole, Alec, 1920
  - Canton Christian College, China, undated
  - Capek, Karel, 1923, 1938-1940
  - Caravans, 1912
  - Carew, Harold D., 1926
  - Carlton, undated
  - Carlyle, Thomas, 1907, 1933-1941, (2 folders)
  - Carman, Bliss, 1928
  - Carmel, Calif, 1927
  - Carmer, Carl, 1936-1937
  - Carolina Moon, 1934
  - Carpenter, Edward, 1918
  - Carroll, Lewis, 1927-1936
  - Carson Pirie Scott and Co., undated
  - Carter, Frederick, 1931
  - Casey, Michael L., 1903-1917, 1927-1937, (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Cather, Willa, 1914, 1932-1940
  - Catalogs, 1909-1910, 1925-1926, undated
  - Catullus, undated
  - Causeries du Jeudi, 1910
  - Cawein, Madison, undated
  - Cestre, Charles, 1908, undated
  - Chamberlain, Juan, 1909-1914, (2 folders)
  - Chandler, Frank W., 1931
  - Chandler, Julian Alvin C., 1929
  - Channel Islands, 1929
  - Channing, William Henry, undated
  - Chaple, Percy, undated
  - de Chardin, Teilhard, 1937-1938
  - King Charles II, 1905, 1927, 1934, undated, (2 folders)
  - Charlton, H.B., undated, (6 folders)
  - Charteris, Evan E., 1940
  - Chase, Emma Service Lester, 1925
  - Chatterton, Thomas, 1902, 1930, undated (Box 55)
  - Chaucer, Geoffrey, 1898, 1907, 1916, 1926, 1936-1940
  - Chelmsford, undated
  - Chelsea Art Club, 1913
  - Le Chemin de Halage, 1913
  - Chess, 1919, 1926-1928
  - Chesterton, Gilbert K., undated
  - Chesterton in France, 1912
  - Chiswick, undated
  - Chilton, Carroll Brent, 1911-1912, undated
  - Chivalry, 1924-1928
  - Christmas, 1934
  - Christian Science, 1906, 1929, 1936-1937
  - Christianity, 1924-1928
  - Cibber, Colley, 1925-1928
  - Citizenship, 1924
  - Civilization, modern, 1922-1923
  - Civilizations, 1922-1925
  - Clancy, Rockwell, 1921-1925
  - Clare, John, 1932-1937
  - Clark, Glover, 1922, 1935-1936
  - Clarke, Creston, 1899, 1941, undated
  - Clark, William Andrew, 1926
  - Clarke, Austin, 1922-1929, 1936-1937
  - Clarke, George Herbert, undated
  - Clarke, University of California, 1926
  - Classical tradition, 1928, 1937
  - Class notes, 1926-1927, (4 folders)
  - Class lists, Union College, Schenectady, N.Y., 1927-1930, undated
  - Cleopatra, 1928
  - Clough, Arthur Hugh, 1899, 1920, n.d. (Box 56)
  - Clough, University of Louisville, Louisville, Ky., reports, undated
  - Clubs, 1908-1910
  - Clutton-Brock, Arthur, 1919-1926
  - Clynes, J. H., 1925
  - Cobb, Starwood, 1936
  - Coeducation, 1903-1907
  - Coffin, Robert P. Tristram, 1936-1940
  - Cohen, Bella, 1922
  - Coleman, Laurence Vail, 1934
  - Coleridge, Samuel T., 1907, 1925-1941, (4 folders)
  - Collett, Anthony, 1926-1927
  - Collins, Wilke, 1927, (2 folders)
  - Colum, Padraic, 1918, 1924-1939 (Box 57)
  - Columbia University, New York, N.Y., 1897-1939, (10 folders)
  - Comedy, 1923-1928 (Box 58)
  - Comfort, Will Levington, 1926
  - Comment, J., 1909-1914
  - Commercial Press, 1922-1932
  - Conclusions, 1924
  - Concordance Society, 1907-1911
  - Confederate, 1930
  - Conger, Henry R., 1905-1910
  - Congreve, William, 1923-1929, 1937
  - Conrad, Joseph, 1914, 1924, 1937
  - Conscription, National Council Against, 1916
  - Consular data, 1907-1909
  - Contemporary civilization, 1926-1930
  - Contemporary prose, undated
  - Continuity in change, 1921
  - Conversation, 1927
  - Conversion, 1924-1925
  - Cookery and food exhibition, 1911
  - Cope, Nancy, 1910-1917 (Box 59)